# SAKIB MOGUL

Full Stack Web Developer

# https://www.linkedin.com/in/zak-mogul/ https://sakibmogul.co.uk/



https://github.com/sakibmul

#### **PROFILE**

Hi, my name is Sakib Mogul (Zak) I am a Full Stack Developer based in the UK. Having worked in the Waste Industry for over twenty years I decided to take the plunge and undertake training in Full Stack Web Development through IT Career Switch. I have experience in Microsoft Office including Excel and various programming languages. I have obtained certificates from Codecademy as well as Microsoft in HTML and CSS.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Waste Contract Supervisor**

Biffa Waste Services 2019 - 2020

- Managing Staff
- Client Meetings
- Use of Microsoft Excel
- Daily Vehicle Allocation.

# **HGV Waste Operative**

Biffa Waste Services 2012 - 2019

- · Driving Assessor and RCV Depot Based Trainer
- · Operation of Vehicles in safe and cost effective manner

# **Machine Operator**

Enterprise plc 2008 – 2012, 2001 - 2005

- Safe operation of Machinery within public areas
- · Updating of Daily Records

#### **Assistant Post Office Manager**

Post Office

2005 - 2007

- · Administration and Accounting Skills gained
- · Face to Face interaction with customers
- Handling of Cash and Mail to ensure the correct procedure was followed
- Learning and using the in house computer system
- Supervision of staff

# **KEY SKILLS**

- Stack Web Development
- · Programming Languages
- Problem Solver
- Microsoft Office including Excel
- Staff Supervision
- Financial Management

# **EDUCATION**

# **Institution**

University of Warwick 1996 - 1999

Qualification

Environmental Studies BSc with Honours

# Institution

Solihull College 1994 - 1996

Qualification

Access to Higher Education Access to Science 12 Credits at level 3 equivalent to 3 A – levels English level CAN pass: equivalent to GCSE grade C Computer Literacy: level one

#### **Institution**

Solihull College
1989 – 1991
Qualification
Maths GCSE grade C
Human Biology GCSE grade C

#### Institution

Malvern Hall Secondary School 1984 – 1989

Qualification

Physics GCSE grade C

# SAKIB MOGUL

Full Stack Web Developer



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE continued

#### **Sales Executive**

Global Media Corporation

2000 - 2001

- · Further improved my Communication Skills
- Communication with key decision makers in large Multi-National Companies

#### **Sales Executive**

Sterling Publications Itd

1999 - 2000

- · Improved my Communication Skills
- Communication with the Chief decision makers of large Multi-National Companies

#### Other Skills

- · Working with VS Code and Notepad ++
- · Microsoft Office including Excel
- · Photographic skills with the use of different lenses
- · Photo editing software such as Adobe and Corel Paintshop
- · Full clean driving licence Cat C

# PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

## Institution

**Microsoft** 

Qualification

MTA Introduction to Programming using HTML and CSS

# **Institution**

Codeccademy

Certification

C#

Java

PHP

Python 3

J Query

**Build Interactive Javascript** 

Websites

Git

Learn the Command Line Web Development Career Path

## Qualification

Class 2 HGV Licence 2012 Drivers CPC valid until 06/2024

#### **Institution**

**NACRO** 

Qualification

City and Guilds level one in Motor Vehicle Maintenance

# REFERENCES

Available Upon Request